### Contact

natalie.tr@sbcglobal.net

www.linkedin.com/in/natalietrann (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Microsoft Word

Research

**Public Speaking** 

### Languages

English (Full Professional)

Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support Experienced Provider (ACLS)

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

# Natalie Tran

BSN Graduate seeking New Grad Residency Position

Greater Los Angeles Area

# Summary

Highly compassionate and specialized BSN graduate. She is a member of the International Sigma Theta Tau Honor Society and a 7-time recipient of the Dean's List award for her academic excellence. During her clinical rotations, she strengthened her emergency-quality medical skills and provided compassion, along with communication skills among the medical team and patient's family through high quality patient-centered care. An achievement she is truly proud of is her strong continuous dedication in healthcare services. She previously held an in-home therapy position in behavioral health close to 2.5 years where she demonstrated outstanding leadership abilities, effective collaboration with the healthcare team, and application of complex problem solving skills.

# Experience

West Coast University
Clinical Rotation
August 2018 - Present (2 years)

Pomona Valley Hospital – Med-Surg, Telemetry, Preceptorship | 136 hours Arrowhead Regional Medical Center – NICU, Postpartum, L&D, OB Course | 68.5 hours

Foothill Regional Medical Center – Pediatric subacute, Pediatric Course | 68.5 hours San Bernardino Community

Hospital – Telemetry, Med-Surg, ICU, Critical Care Course | 136 hours

San Gabriel Valley Medical Center – OR, ER, ICU, Telemetry, Med-Surg, Med-Surg II Course | 136 hours

Kindred Ontario – Med-surg, ICU,

Med-Surg I Course | 136 hours

Royal Oaks Skilled Nursing Facility - SNF, Fundamental Course | 90 hours

Public Health Course | 91 Community hours

Mental Health Course | 91 Community hours

Assessment, Consultation & Treatment (ACT)
Registered Behavior Technician
October 2016 - January 2019 (2 years 4 months)
Page 1 of 2

#### Pasadena, CA

- Carry out Applied Behavioral Analysis (ABA) intervention care plans for in home therapy for children who fall on the autism spectrum in order to minimize patient's maladaptive behaviors and promote healthy living.
- Highlighted by patient's families for my kindness and compassion while assisting patients with skills for everyday life, applying them to goal oriented behaviors, and educating family on care plan implementations.

Arts for Humanity!
Student Intern
September 2015 - June 2016 (10 months)
Monroe Elementary

- Offer ongoing opportunities for personal growth through the arts with elementary students that have developmental disabilities
- Construct a class curriculum with art and physical activities that are accommodating and comfortable to each student's requirement
- Cooperate with classroom teacher and staffs to cultivate creativity and provide the support the student needs

Devereux Advanced Behavioral Health Direct Support Professional October 2015 - May 2016 (8 months) Goleta, CA

- Provide care to individuals of all ages with autism spectrum disorders, developmental disabilities, and other mental health challenges
- Assist individuals to independently carry out everyday tasks or occupations
- Implement behavioral/treatment plan based on client's needs and lifestyle

## Education

West Coast University

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2018 - 2020)

UC Santa Barbara

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Psychology and Applied Psychology · (2012 - 2016)